Now, this really smooths out the skin.
And you have to rub it in really good, obviously, because it looks like milk and you don't want to go out with anything white on you.
And honestly, you can rub it all over.
And you'll see, in about 20 minutes, how smooth and soft your skin feels.
Every time I wear this and somebody touches my skin, they say how soft it feels.
So, just rub it in really well.
And you can--and the great thing is also, I mean, you can use this on your face--here, lay back a little bit.
You can rub it into your face as well.
And it's not oily so you're not going to have any of that build-up.
It's just a nice, soothing feel.
I'll show you an alternative to this as well.
I love the milk products.
Here we go.
I mean, there are a lot of body creams out there and I'm going to show you a couple of those also.
But the milk--the reason why the milk is so great is because of the proteins and the vitamins in it that most of the lotions don't have.
So, make sure you get the milk.
There are a couple of different variations you can get.
Go to your local beauty store.
That milk product was only about $12.99. So, you can find them high end or low end. Just make sure when you read the back that it says, "Proteins and vitamins A, D and E" in it.